<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GAPS (EPICS) Camera</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/gaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/gaps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My team collaborated with Universidad del Norte in Barranquilla, Colombia to monitor the ecosystem around the university. I used Onshape to design multiple low-cost wildlife camera housings utilizing bird feeders to prevent theft. These housings were designed to be easy to manufacture through a variety of methods such as additively through a consumer FDM printer or on a jigsaw with a paper template to match the project partner’s needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miso Mechanics 9442 - 2024 Robot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/miso/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/miso/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At the end of 2023, I founded a rookie FIRST Robotics team and fundraised over $30K for competition and robot costs. During the 2024 season, I designed multiple subsystems on our award-winning competition robot which ranked as high as  20th offensively out of 3,500 teams worldwide. I also developed computer vision systems using PhotonVision to detect game objectives and utilized it in autonomous routines, allowing for real-time decision making to aid in gameplay.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PER25 Chassis Closeouts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/per25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/per25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I designed chassis closeouts using NX, validating them in ANSYS to meet both structural and aerodynamic requirements. This role enhanced my mechanical design capabilities and further strengthened my proficiency at CAD. I also manufactured closeouts, chassis tubes, and other parts of the PER 2025 competition car using various composites or manufacturing techniques.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soil Microbiome Analysis Robot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/pipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/pipe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I used Onshape to designed the slip ring assembly for the reel of the robot to allow for easy unspooling for long distance data acquisition. I also worked on the data parser to sync the data collected by the robot&amp;rsquo;s onboard sensors and it&amp;rsquo;s cameras for more precise research and location identification. I presented our findings at the United States Department of Agriculture’s Ames National Laboratory with two more senior lab members.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
