<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 10:23:39 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ztos</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/client-work/ztos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 10:23:39 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/client-work/ztos/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/client-work/zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 10:23:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/client-work/zoo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanba</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/client-work/kanba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 10:22:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/client-work/kanba/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldline</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/client-work/goldline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 10:21:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/client-work/goldline/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth 2.0</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/client-work/earth2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 10:17:12 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/client-work/earth2.0/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asgardia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/client-work/asgardia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/client-work/asgardia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAPS (EPICS) Camera</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/gaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/gaps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My team collaborated with Universidad del Norte in Barranquilla, Colombia to monitor the ecosystem around the university. I used Onshape to design multiple low-cost wildlife camera housings utilizing bird feeders to prevent theft. These housings were designed to be easy to manufacture through a variety of methods such as additively through a consumer FDM printer or on a jigsaw with a paper template to match the project partner’s needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miso Mechanics 9442 - 2024 Robot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/miso/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/miso/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At the end of 2023, I founded a rookie FIRST Robotics team and fundraised over $30K for competition and robot costs. During the 2024 season, I designed multiple subsystems on our award-winning competition robot which ranked as high as 20th offensively out of 3,500 teams worldwide. I also developed computer vision and localization systems using PhotonVision to detect game objectives and utilized it in autonomous routines, allowing for real-time decision making to aid in gameplay.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PER25 Chassis Closeouts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/per25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/per25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I designed chassis closeouts and the battery mounts using NX, validating them in ANSYS to meet both structural and aerodynamic requirements. This role enhanced my mechanical design capabilities and further strengthened my proficiency at CAD. I also manufactured closeouts, chassis tubes, welding jig, and other parts of the PER 2025 competition car using various composites or manufacturing techniques.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soil Microbiome Measuring Robot (SoMMR)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/pipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/pipe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I used Onshape to designed the slip ring assembly for the reel of the robot to allow for easy unspooling for long distance data acquisition and worked on a data parser to sync the data collected by the robot&amp;rsquo;s onboard sensors and cameras for more precise research and location identification. I presented our findings at the United States Department of Agriculture’s Ames National Laboratory with two other senior lab members.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chassis Designer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h5 id=&#34;skills-cad-onshape-fea-ansys-composites-manufacturing-cfd&#34;&gt;Skills: CAD, Onshape, FEA, Ansys, Composites Manufacturing, CFD&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I designed chassis closeouts using NX to isolate cockpit and driver from potentially hazardous road debris. I then validated the closeouts using ANSYS to match specified rigidity targets as well as for aerodynamic purposes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Product Designer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h5 id=&#34;skills-cad-onshape-rapid-prototyping-technical-documentation-product-design&#34;&gt;Skills: CAD, Onshape, Rapid Prototyping, Technical Documentation, Product Design&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My team collaborated with Universidad del Norte in Barranquilla, Colombia to monitor the ecosystem around the university. I used Onshape to design multiple low-cost wildlife camera housings utilizing bird feeders to prevent theft. These housings were designed to be easy to manufacture through a variety of methods such as additively through a consumer FDM printer or on a jigsaw with a paper template to match the project partner&amp;rsquo;s needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research Assistant</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/job-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h5 id=&#34;skills-embedded-programming-microcontrollers-cad-onshape-rapid-prototyping-technical-documentation&#34;&gt;Skills: Embedded Programming, Microcontrollers, CAD, Onshape, Rapid Prototyping, Technical Documentation&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I developed low-cost inertia measuring and position estimation solutions to study animal behavior patterns as well as designed soft robotic limbs to assist in locomotion when traversing difficult terrain. I also researched quadruped motion with artifical limbs to enhance agility and manueverability under Associate Professor Upinder Kaur.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
